

CONTACT



(+95)945 480 1960



khantzawhein261@gmail.com



steven20201.github.io/Portfolio/



No-10, Main Road, Zaiganine, Bago, Myanmar.

SKILLS

- C#, Vb.Net
- WordPress, Laravel, PHP
- MySQL
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Team Work

LANGUAGE

- English
- Burmese
- China

KHANT ZAW HEIN

WEB DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a growth web developer with 1 years of experience in marketing in the Australia market. Creative, sharp-minded person with quick learning skills & cooperative with teams. Strong time-management skills and responsible with my work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Web Developer (Independent Contractor)

March 2022 - Oct 2022

Effectively managed team with 7 employers in 6 locations in 2 countries. Company training, public relations with social media, creative posts in social media & CRM. Developed web design idea & web Pages. Created more than 10 websites using WordPress and designed some frameworks in Figma. I have done minimum 7 websites and all the websites have good reviews from the clients.

Web Developer | Internship September 2021 - December 2021

I have created one E-Commerce website & learning about Laravel and Node.js. I have to do the hosting for the customers and need to edit the domain details if the customers want to change the domain name.

EDUCATION

Diploma in Information Technology, Sunway College Johor Bahru, Malaysia

AUGUST 2019 - DECEMBER 2021

Java (A), Database (A), System Development (A), Web Design (A), Implementation project (A), User Interface Design(A), Discrete Math(A)

REFERENCES

Ryan Rahman (SME Tech Solution) office@smetechsolution.com.au +61 400 213 350

Joslyn Chai Keyi (Website Team Supervisor) Kevi Technology joslyn@kevi.my (+60)014-9117275